[
  {
    "question": "メトグルコ",
    "correct": "メトホルミン",
    "choices": [
      "メトホルミン",
      "ブホルミン",
      "ニセルゴリン",
      "モキシフロキサシン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ポリフル",
    "correct": "ポリカルボフィルカルシウム",
    "choices": [
      "ポリカルボフィルカルシウム",
      "アトルバスタチンカルシウム",
      "ピタバスタチンカルシウム",
      "ロスバスタチンカルシウム"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "デザレックス",
    "correct": "デスロラタジン",
    "choices": [
      "デスロラタジン",
      "ビオチン",
      "ロラタジン",
      "ジオクチルソジウムスルホサクシネート"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "レザルタス",
    "correct": "オルメサルタンメドキソミルアゼルニジピン",
    "choices": [
      "マニジピン",
      "オルメサルタンメドキソミルアゼルニジピン",
      "アゼルニジピン",
      "シルニジピン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "アリナミン",
    "correct": "フルスルチアミン",
    "choices": [
      "エデトカルシウム",
      "フルスルチアミン",
      "ベンフォチアミン",
      "ダサチニブ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ビラノア",
    "correct": "ビラスチン",
    "choices": [
      "オンダンセトロン",
      "アゼラスチン",
      "ベナゼプリル",
      "ビラスチン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "エビリファイ",
    "correct": "アリピプラゾール",
    "choices": [
      "ラベプラゾール",
      "アリピプラゾール",
      "オメプラゾール",
      "ランソプラゾール"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "アルロイド",
    "correct": "アルギン",
    "choices": [
      "ヒドロコルチゾン・フラジオマイシン",
      "ジクアホソル",
      "アルギン",
      "イソロイシン・ロイシン・バリン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "マーズレン",
    "correct": "アズレンスルホングルタミン",
    "choices": [
      "グルタミン",
      "アズレンスルホングルタミン",
      "アズレンスルホン・グルタミン",
      "テルミサルタン・アムロジピンベシル"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "アスベリン",
    "correct": "チペピジンヒベンズ",
    "choices": [
      "ロキサチジン",
      "ピレンゼピン",
      "ロピニロール",
      "チペピジンヒベンズ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ボノサップパック",
    "correct": "ボノプラザンアモキシシリンクラリスロマイシンシート",
    "choices": [
      "エルデカルシトール",
      "ブロナンセリン",
      "ボノプラザンアモキシシリンクラリスロマイシンシート",
      "ヒドロキシジンパモ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ラックビ",
    "correct": "ビフィズス",
    "choices": [
      "プロカテロール",
      "メトプロロール",
      "ビフィズス",
      "イミダプリル"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ユリス",
    "correct": "ドチヌラド",
    "choices": [
      "バゼドキシフェン",
      "ドチヌラド",
      "トリヘキシフェニジル",
      "サラゾスルファピリジン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ボンビバ",
    "correct": "イバンドロン",
    "choices": [
      "オキシブチニン",
      "アレンドロン",
      "イバンドロン",
      "ラベプラゾール"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "フオイパン",
    "correct": "カモスタットメシル",
    "choices": [
      "ニザチジン",
      "ミコフェノールモフェチル",
      "メロキシカム",
      "カモスタットメシル"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "アセチルスピラマイシン",
    "correct": "スピラマイシンエステル",
    "choices": [
      "リボフラビンエステル",
      "スピラマイシンエステル",
      "クロルフェネシンカルバミンエステル",
      "トコフェロールニコチンエステル"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "インデラル",
    "correct": "プロプラノロール",
    "choices": [
      "アテノロール",
      "レボブノロール",
      "アロチノロール",
      "プロプラノロール"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ミカトリオ",
    "correct": "テルミサルタンアムロジピンベシルヒドロクロロチアジド",
    "choices": [
      "ロサルタン・ヒドロクロロチアジド",
      "テルミサルタンアムロジピンベシルヒドロクロロチアジド",
      "カンデサルタンシレキセチル・ヒドロクロロチアジド",
      "ヒドロクロロチアジド"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "フラジール",
    "correct": "メトロニダゾール",
    "choices": [
      "フルコナゾール",
      "チニダゾール",
      "メトロニダゾール",
      "ナルフラフィン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "アナフラニール",
    "correct": "クロミプラミン",
    "choices": [
      "オルメサルタンメドキソミル",
      "ラクトミン",
      "カルシトリオール",
      "クロミプラミン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ガナトン",
    "correct": "イトプリド",
    "choices": [
      "ホモクロルシクリジン",
      "ヒドロクロロチアジド",
      "セリプロロール",
      "イトプリド"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ニポラジン",
    "correct": "メキタジン",
    "choices": [
      "エタノール",
      "フルボキサミン",
      "ドネペジル",
      "メキタジン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ノイロビタン",
    "correct": "オクトチアミン",
    "choices": [
      "エゼチミブ",
      "フルスルチアミン",
      "ベンフォチアミン",
      "オクトチアミン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "アマージ",
    "correct": "ナラトリプタン",
    "choices": [
      "リザトリプタン",
      "ゾルミトリプタン",
      "ナラトリプタン",
      "エレトリプタン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ナトリックス",
    "correct": "インダパミド",
    "choices": [
      "インダパミド",
      "モメタゾンフランカルボンエステル",
      "ラミブジン・アバカビル",
      "ジクアホソル"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "メルカゾール",
    "correct": "チアマゾール",
    "choices": [
      "シタフロキサシン",
      "チアマゾール",
      "ジメチコン",
      "クロトリマゾール"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ピドキサール",
    "correct": "ピリドキサールエステル",
    "choices": [
      "トコフェロールニコチンエステル",
      "クロルフェネシンカルバミンエステル",
      "リボフラビンエステル",
      "ピリドキサールエステル"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "プラノバール",
    "correct": "ノルゲストレルエチニルエストラジオール",
    "choices": [
      "エストラジオール",
      "エゼチミブ",
      "ノルエチステロン・エチニルエストラジオール",
      "ノルゲストレルエチニルエストラジオール"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ハイボン",
    "correct": "リボフラビンエステル",
    "choices": [
      "ピリドキサールリンエステル",
      "クロルフェネシンカルバミンエステル",
      "リボフラビンエステル",
      "トコフェロールニコチンエステル"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "カイトリル",
    "correct": "グラニセトロン",
    "choices": [
      "リファンピシン",
      "ロスバスタチンカルシウム",
      "グラニセトロン",
      "オンダンセトロン"
    ]
  }
]